{"questions":[{"question":"What is the major advantage of Agile?","level":"1","answers":["Enables sequential development","Allows agile development that adjusted to customer","Allows test driven development","There are no major advantage to agile"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"In Agile methodology:","level":"2","answers":["Documentation requirements is always up to date","Documentation requirements includes very detailed content of project","Documentation requirements is not usually up to date","Documentation requirements is usually up to date once in month"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"What is the main difference between the Waterfall and the Scrum approach?","level":"1","answers":["Scrum is not flexible like the Waterfall methodology","The waterfall is performed in iterations and Scrum performed without iterations","The waterfall is performed sequentially and Scrum performed iteratively","There is no difference"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"In agile when sprint is finish we:","level":"2","answers":["Begin immediately the next sprint","Rest until receiving feedback from the client","Begin the next sprint until receiving feedback from the client","Perform retrospective on sprint performance"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"What are functional requirements?","level":"2","answers":["Statements of services the system should provide","Constraints on services the system should provide","Constraints on the functions offered by the system","Constraints on the system from the domain of operation"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"UC diagram describes:","level":"1","answers":["Functional and non-functional requirements","Only functional requirements","Only non-functional requirements", "Non of the above"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"When does New requirements emerge?","level":"2","answers":["Only when the system is being developed ","Before planning","After production","When the customer asks for them"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"What is the main purpose of code review?","level":"2","answers":["Reviewer","Software developer and reviewer","Product manager","Client"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"what MVC model contain?","level":"1","answers":["View - Controller - Model","Candy - View - Model","Controller - Model - View","View - Controller - Moodle"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"Which of the following statements about SOA is inncorrect?","level":"3","answers":["System applications are divided into services","Services are autonomous","Services can be assembled and reused","The internal structure of the service is visible to the consumer"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"What design pattern is the best to limit the number of an object instances?","level":"1","answers":["Proxy","Factory","Singleton","Observe"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"Software architecture consists of:","level":"1","answers":["Software elements","The code of the software","Software elements and relations among them","Documentation of the software"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"What is correct from the following sentences?","level":"2","answers":["IASS provide Provides a development platform to different programming language","IASS provide mainly basic infrastructure","PASS provide only storage", "Non of the above"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"What is the difference between the maintenance of public and private cloud?","level":"2","answers":["Public cloud requires more maintenance","Private cloud requires more maintenance","Both of them require the same amount of maintenance","They donâ€™t need any maintenance"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"Where SaaS makes sense?","level":"3","answers":["Applications that have a significant need for web or mobile access","Applications where extremely fast processing of real time data is required","Applications where legislation does not permit data being hosted externally", "Narnia"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"What is the advantage of a public cloud?","level":"1","answers":["Lack of control ","Slow speed","No maintenance","Weaker security"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"What is Required of Maintenance Programmers?","level":"2","answers":["Super debugging skills","The ability to determine the cause of failure of a large product","The ability to function effectively without adequate documentation","All the answers are correct"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"What are maintenance risks?","level":"1","answers":["Schedule","Loss of control","Future maintenance difficulties","High quality"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"What is the most important phase of software production?","level":"2","answers":["Maintenance","Development","Testing","All of them are important"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"Software engineering refers to:","level":"1","answers":["Only writing code","Software tests","The whole life cycle of software","Software design"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"Unit tests usually include:","level":"1","answers":["Testing software interface","System integration of complex software parts","Only components","Methods, classes, simple components"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"The unit test should be planned:","level":"3","answers":["Before development","After development","During development","Never"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"Who use White - box testing?","level":"1","answers":["Usually by the Scrum master","Preferably by an independent tester","Usually by the customer","Usually by the developer"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"Equivalence class is:","level":"3","answers":["Used in white box tests to examine the inputs represent","Used in Black box tests to examine the inputs represent","Used in Black box tests to examine all possible inputs","Used in white box tests to examine all possible inputs"],"team":"Wolf","correct_ans":"2"}]}